* English Italiano Polskie Tiếng Việt Srpski Bahasa Indonesia Pусский Română Português 正體中文 简体中文 한국어 日本語 ภาษาไท Español Turkish Francais Persian

[ULTRA_VIEWER_
=============](https://ultraviewer.net/en/)

Privacy
=======

[Homepage](https://ultraviewer.net/) _/_ Privacy

###### UltraViewer respects and takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy applies to all products and services provided by UltraViewer. Please read the following privacy policy to understand the commitment that we made to respect and protect your information:

Privacy policy of UltraViewer
-----------------------------

**1\. When you register a new account on UltraViewer**, we will ask you to provide personal information such as your name, email, phone number, preferred language, and more. We will use this information to assist you, send notifications, process payments, and conduct promotional activities related to our products and services.

**2\. By using the service** , you agree to use cookies, which is used to store information on your browser for some features like "remember me" when login, or remember which language you prefer to display on the website.

**3\. UltraViewer committed no exchange or selling your personal data to third parties** . We do not share, sell, commercialize your personal information to any other parties.

**4\. Your password when registering on UltraViewer is encrypted securely**. We apply one-way encryption layer so is's not able to decrypt your password from the database. Using a strong password length includes both characters and numbers which will help you to protect your password from risks.

**5\. Your remote sessions are fully encrypted with SSL, we do not record your remote session video nor store it on our servers**

GDPR and UltraViewer: Your Data Protection Assurance
----------------------------------------------------

##### What is GDPR:

GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) stands as a comprehensive data privacy regulation within the European Union, crafted to safeguard the personal data of EU citizens and empower them with greater authority over their personal information. This regulation replaces prior fragmented data protection laws in EU Member States and extends its reach to organizations operating within the EU that handle personal data.

##### UltraViewer's Commitment to GDPR Compliance:

At **UltraViewer**, we have diligently implemented both technical and organizational measures to ensure that our data processing practices adhere to the stipulations of the **General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**.

##### Our Alignment with GDPR Provisions:

* **Ethical Data Processing:** We are committed to processing personal data in a lawful, impartial, and transparent manner.
* **Purpose Restriction:** We strictly limit the collection and processing of personal data to well-defined purposes.
* **Minimalistic Data Collection:** We uphold the principle of data minimization, only gathering information that is essential for the specified objectives.
* **Data Precision and Storage Constraints:** We maintain the accuracy of data and observe limitations on storage duration.
* **Robust Data Protection Measures:** Appropriate technical and organizational measures have been put in place to ensure robust data protection.
* **Obligation to Report Breaches:** We adhere to the obligation of promptly notifying both the supervisory authority and affected individuals in the event of data breaches.
* **Upholding Individual Rights:** We respect and uphold the rights of individuals, including but not limited to the right to access and the right to be forgotten.

For an in-depth understanding of how we align with GDPR, please refer to our Privacy Policy.

##### Safeguarding Your Personal Data with UltraViewer:

We are steadfast in our efforts to guarantee that the personal data we collect is pertinent and necessary for its intended purposes. We employ a series of measures designed to shield personal data, including:

* **Encryption:** Personal data is encrypted during both transit and storage phases.
* **Secure Infrastructure:** Our data centers adhere to industry-standard security protocols, including fire suppression systems and multi-factor authentication.
* **Controlled Access:** Personal data access is granted solely to authorized personnel, contingent upon job-related responsibilities.
* **Periodic Security Audits:** Regular security audits are conducted to identify and promptly address potential vulnerabilities.
* **Incident Response Strategy:** We maintain a comprehensive plan to effectively manage security incidents, such as data breaches, to mitigate harm and expedite resolution.
* **Adherence to Privacy Laws:** We ensure full compliance with pertinent privacy and data protection regulations, including **GDPR**.

**UltraViewer's** commitment to safeguarding data extends across various data protection policies, assuring that personal data is collected, processed, and stored in alignment with GDPR directives. These policies are routinely reviewed and updated to maintain **GDPR** compliance.

It is crucial to recognize that users play a pivotal role in safeguarding their personal data. This involves maintaining the security of passwords and exercising caution when confronted with phishing attempts and other security risks.

**The remote desktop control software UltraViewer** has reached a new milestone in terms of global user base. We are constantly working to improve the product to meet users' needs. Please feel free to send us your feedback and suggestions.  

About UltraViewer
-----------------

UltraViewer is a popular and continually developing free remote desktop control software. We're leading in technology innovation of the global. We will give you the best things to improve your life quality.

Product
-------

Help
----

Contact us
----------

* +84 4.7300.9199

Follow us
---------

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

#### Newsletter  
Signup

#### Our Clients  
Partners

* 
* 
* 

**@ Copyright UltraViewer 2024 | All Rights ReservedTM**
